[
    {
        "front": "おわり",
        "back": "end",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "おりる",
        "back": "to go down",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "すべる",
        "back": "to slip",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "せなか",
        "back": "back",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "うつ",
        "back": "to hit",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "なげる",
        "back": "to throw",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "ほね",
        "back": "bone",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "ち",
        "back": "blood",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "つづく",
        "back": "to continue (i.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）つづける",
        "back": "to continue (t.)",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "すっかり",
        "back": "completely",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "とどく",
        "back": "to arrive",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～を）とどける",
        "back": "to deliver",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "だいぶ",
        "back": "much; quite",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "もうすぐ",
        "back": "soon",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "うごく",
        "back": "to move; to be active",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "（おなかが）すく",
        "back": "to get hungry",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "かわく",
        "back": "to dry up",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    },
    {
        "front": "つらい",
        "back": "tough",
        "chapter": "N4 C29"
    }
]